ALEXANDER BERG

QA Engineer/ QA automation Engineer

Quality Assurance engineer with IT knowledge.
IT geek for 12 years. Looking forward to joining a company and use my creativity and experience to improve the overall quality of a product or service. All my skills, code, and contacts on my personal web-site.



CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

alexandr.berg92@gmail.com

Address

Saint Petersburg, Russia

Phone

+79062452865

Date of birth

Jun 22, 1992

Link

alexander-berg.github.io

SKILLS

- Working knowledge of Web Automation
- Excellent analytical skills
- Experienced in bug reporting and finding errors
- Multiple IT skills

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced

Russian

Native



EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

QA automation Engineer

freelance

Completed multiple testing projects, including automation and mobile

2020 - 2021

QA Engineer

Netology Online university

Studied Software development, software testing, and helped company with current goals.

2016 - 2020

• QA tester

Ubisoft, Wargaming

Tested games in closed alpha programs, created bug-reports, tested connection issues. reported graphical, visual, performance and ui bugs.

Saint Petersburg 2016 - 2018

Sales Assistant

OOO "Palmira"

Engaged in sales of digital equipment, smartphones, laptops and services

Saint Petersburg 2014 - 2015

Low current systems engineer assistant
OOO "Bors"

Engaged in the installation of low-current security and fire safety systems, worked with servers.

Saint Petersburg 2013 - 2014

Technical Support

000 "Teletrade"

Assisted clients with complex technical issues requiring in-depth problem solving

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021

• QA engineer

Netology Online university

Herzen State University

Studied Software development, software testing, Java, C#, CI/CD, tests automation.

Saint Petersburg

2012 - 2013

Meteorologist

2010 - 2011

Saint Petersburg

Russian State Hydrometeorological University

Municipal & government managment